You're in for a shock.
Jolt is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Tanya Wexler.
A bouncer with an anger management problem goes on a furious and
resentful rampage after the murder of a friend.
Lindy, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Dr. Ivan Munchin, played by Stanley Tucci.
Detective Vicars, played by Bobby Cannavale.
Justin, played by Jai Courtney.
Detective Nevin, played by Laverne Cox.
Gareth Fizel, played by David Bradley.
Jolt is a 2021 American action comedy film directed by
Tanya Wexler and written by Scott Wascha.
The film stars Kate Beckinsale, Susan Sarandon, Bobby Cannavale,
Laverne Cox, Stanley Tucci, and Jai Courtney.
It was released on July 23, 2021, by Amazon Studios.
The film explores themes of homicide, dark comedy, crime
boss, female protagonist, electro shock.
The tone is dark and intense.